我要去庆祝活动，我们都庆祝并告诉Marito，Che Marito，我带来了我的衬衫，我想我把她留在了银行里。
I'm going to the celebrations, we all celebrate and tell Marito, Che Marito, I brought my shirt that I think I left her in the bank.
Me voy a los festejos, festejamos todos y le digo a Marito, che Marito, me traje la camiseta que creo que la dejé en el banco.
马里托去看里面，因为那不是。
And Marito went to look inside because that was not.
y Marito fue a buscar una adentro porque esa no estaba.
我说...
I said ...
Yo dije...
混乱。
Chao.
那件衬衫消失了。
That shirt disappeared.
Desapareció esa camiseta.
不，我快死了。
No, I'm dying.
No, me muero.
我给了它，因为他们滴了我，就是这样。
I gave it because they drip me, that's it.
Yo la di porque me la chorearon, ya está.
一些玩家梦想赢得冠军或其他任何人。
Some players dream of winning a title or whatever.
Algunos jugadores sueñan con ganar un título o lo que sea.
对我而言，随着这个年龄，我所有人都给了我，大多数最重要的是...
And to me, with this age, that I have all given me like that, most, all the most important, is ...
Y a mí, con esta edad, que se me hayan dado todos así, la mayoría, todos los más importantes, es...
有些很好。
Something very nice.
Algo muy lindo.
他告诉我，他必须放一个并扔掉蜘蛛，这是对的。
He told me, he got to put one and threw the spider, which is something right.
Me decía él, llegaba a meter uno y me tiraba la araña, que es algo correcto.
朱利安是什么？
What does Julian, well?
¿Qué hace Julián, bien?
仍然。
Still.
Todavía.
它给了我一种感觉，因为这是一种感觉。
It gives me the feeling, for this it is a sensation.
Me da la sensación, para esto es una sensación.
您是否有点害怕会发生什么？
Are you a little afraid of what is going to happen or not?
¿Tenés un poco de miedo de lo que vaya a pasar o no?
这个孩子今天会来什么？
What will this kid come today or not?
¿Con qué va a venir este pibe hoy o no?
有点，访问者？
A little, ¿Visists?
Un poco, ¿viste?
我看到了你的一些问题，有些一半。
I saw some questions of yours, some half things.
Vi algunas preguntas tuyas, algunas cosas medias.
疑问，您必须注意。
For doubts, you have to be attentive.
Por las dudas, hay que estar atentos.
有些事情之类的东西稀有，但它们比其他任何事情都要多。
Some things like rare, but they are more games than anything else.
algunas cositas como raras, pero son más juegos que otra cosa.
是的，它们是游戏，但有时您必须做出决定。
Yes, they are games, but sometimes you have to make decisions.
Sí, son juegos, pero a veces hay que tomar decisiones.
好吧，一个人可能会被卡住。
And well, one can be stuck.
Y bueno, uno puede quedar pegado.
是的，分析。
Yes, to analyze.
Sí, para igual de analizar.
显然，在来到这里之前，我不仅读过，而且我看到了很多您的采访。
Before coming here, obviously, I not only read, but I saw a lot of interviews of yours.
Antes de venir acá, obviamente, no solo leí, sino que vi un montón de entrevistas tuyas.
在卡尔钦举行的庆祝活动，该市的演讲，马德里的演讲。
Of the celebrations in Calchín, the presentation at the City, the presentation at Madrid.
de los festejos en Calchín, la presentación en el City, la presentación en el Madrid.
这显然使您感到震惊，今天打开Tiktok并谈论。
That clearly shames you, today to open a Tiktok and talk.
que claramente te da vergüenza, a hoy abrir un TikTok y ya hablar.
您已经更加松散，更换了。
You are already a little more loose and more changer with that.
Ya estás un poco más suelto y más canchero con eso.
而且一点一点地，我们稍加一会儿，但是很一点一点，很安静。
And little by little, little by little we are getting a little, but very little by little, very quiet.
Y de a poco, de a poco nos vamos metiendo un poco, pero muy de a poco, muy tranquilo.
那是什么告诉你的？
Is that what tell you?
¿Te pasa eso que te dicen?
现在您在Atlético，我们进入了这一章。
Now you are in Atlético and we get into that chapter.
Ahora estás en el Atlético y nos metemos en ese capítulo.
朱利安，我们必须介绍你。
Julian, we have to present you.
Julián, te tenemos que presentar.
当然。
And of course.
Y claro.
你必须说话。
You have to talk.
Hay que hablar.
那一刻是羞耻还是简单地害羞，说它发生了很快？
Does that moment be shame or simply shy and say that it happens fast?
¿Te da vergüenza ese momento o simplemente sos tímido y decís que pase rápido?
是的，一点。
Yes, a little that.
Sí, un poco eso.
我很害羞，我更喜欢它会很快发生，但与此同时，您必须这样做。
I am shy, I prefer that it will happen fast, but at the same time you have to do it.
Soy tímido, prefiero que pase rápido, pero al mismo tiempo hay que hacerlo.
我们必须对人承担这项责任，这意味着所有的意思，我们就在这里。
We have to take that responsibility for people, for everything that means and here we are.
Hay que tomar esa responsabilidad por la gente, por todo lo que significa y acá estamos.
显然，这是一个非常不错的俱乐部，Atlético。
Clearly this is a very nice club, Atlético.
claramente este es un club muy lindo, el Atlético.
看来他很阿根廷。
And it seems that he is very Argentine.
Y parece ser que es muy argentino.
不仅是因为阿尔替托拥有的阿根廷数量。
Not only because of the Argentine amount that Atlético has.
No solo por la cantidad argentina que tiene el Atlético.
但是，由于爪子对这个俱乐部所代表的一切，看来它尽可能尽可能。
but because by the claw, for everything that this club represents, it seems that it is as Argentine as possible.
sino porque por la garra, por todo lo que representa este club, pareciera ser que es lo más argentino posible.
你感觉就像...
You feel that like ...
Sentís eso como...
怎么在家？
How to be at home?
¿Como estar en casa?
是的，是的，好吧，有点。
Yes, yes, well, well, a little.
Sí, sí, bastante, bueno, un poco.
从您说的话来看，除此之外，我们是阿根廷人，您所代表的内容，人们向您展示什么...
From what you say, beyond that we are a lot of Argentines, what you represent, what people show you ...
Por lo que decís, más allá de que somos mucho argentinos, esto de lo que representas, lo que la gente te muestra...
人民，粉丝和一切的爱，是的，足够了。
The love of the people, the fans and everything, yes, enough.
el cariño de la gente, la hinchada y todo, sí, bastante, bastante.
朱利亚诺（Juliano）打电话给你，朱利安诺·西蒙内（Juliano Simeone）一半，他说服你来了，这发生在你身上。
And it happened to you, Juliano called you, Juliano Simeone, half that he convinced for you to come.
Y a vos te pasó, Juliano te llamó, Juliano Simeone, medio que convenció para que vos vengas.
因为他说他的通行证有一定比例。
Because he says he has a percentage of your pass.
Porque él dice que tiene un porcentaje de tu pase.
是的，对吗？
This is so, right?
Esto es así, ¿verdad?
不，我仍然没有将其解决。
No, I still didn't fix that to him.
No, todavía no lo arreglé eso con él.
但是，是的，我们在奥运会上分享，这是我到达那里的第一天。
But yes, we share at the Olympic Games and it is the first day I got there.
Pero sí, compartimos en los Juegos Olímpicos y es el primer día que llegué ahí.
法国每天都在脱身。
France was getting shed every day.
A Francia estaba todos los días metiéndome ficha.
在奥运会之后，我做出了决定。
It was a bit there, a little after the Olympic Games, which I made the decision.
Fue un poco ahí, un poco después de los Juegos Olímpicos, que tomé la decisión.
您做了什么或想到了Bernabéu的监狱，因为我真的告诉​​您Bernabéu在玩所有事情
What you did or had it thought about the prison in the Bernabéu because I really tell you Bernabéu playing everything
en lo que hiciste o lo tenías pensado picar el penal en el Bernabéu porque realmente te digo Bernabéu jugándose todo
你在俱乐部里有几天，人们已经爱你了
You have a few days in the club and people already love you
vos tenés pocos días en el club y la gente ya te ama
是否已经想到了，或者沃克说我是高峰和上帝想要的？
Was it already thought or the walker said I was peak and whatever God wants?
¿Ya era pensado o en la caminante dijiste yo se la pico y que sea lo que Dios quiera?
不，我已经考虑到了两天前，如果有罚款，我去了中间。
No, I had already thought about it as two days before, if there is a penalty I go to the middle.
No, ya lo había pensado como dos días antes, si hay un penal voy al medio.
并在培训一些。
And in training some.
y en los entrenamientos partí algunos.
在最后一个我要尝试的地方。
And in the last I piqué to try.
y en el último la piqué para probar.
第二天，前一天，一个人也离开了胡安·穆索（Juan Musso），也离开了...
And the next day, the previous day, one also left Juan Musso and also ...
Y al otro día, el día previo, también le partió uno a Juan Musso y también se la...
他把它扔到了中间。
He throws it into the middle.
Se la tira al medio.
是的，我有点紧张，但是好吧，因为它抬起了你的头，那就是...
Yes, I was a little nervous, but well, because it raises your head and that's ...
Sí, estaba un poco nervioso, pero bueno, porque por ahí levanta la cabeza y está...
除了尺寸为两米的Courois，有一千场比赛。
Apart is Courtois that measures two meters, has a thousand games.
Aparte es Courtois que mide dos metros, tiene mil partidos.
你说，我去了中间和喙。
You said, I go to the middle and the beak.
Dijiste, yo voy al medio y la pico.
是的，是的，我坚信，很积极，这将是一个目标，幸运的是，他进入了。
Yes, yes, I was convinced, positive, that it was going to be a goal there and, well, luckily he entered.
Sí, sí, estaba convencido, positivo, que iba a ser gol ahí y, bueno, por suerte entró.
有关于伯纳邦庆祝活动的话题。
There is talk of the celebration in the Bernabéu.
Se habla del festejo en el Bernabéu.
这是狮子座的庆祝活动。
which is the celebration of Leo.
que es el festejo de Leo.
你是为狮子座做的吗？
Did you do it for Leo?
¿Lo hiciste por Leo?
梅西这样做的典型庆祝活动？
The typical celebration that Messi does so?
¿El típico festejo que Messi hace así?
不，不，不。
No, no, no.
不，好，我妈妈前几天告诉他，看来你有球...
No, just good, my mom told him the other day, it seems that you have the ball ...
No, justo bueno, mi mamá le dije el otro día, parece que tenés la bola...
神奇的球是因为在与勒沃库森（Leverkusen）比赛之前，他给我写了
The magical ball because before the game with Leverkusen he wrote me
la bola mágica porque antes del partido con Leverkusen me escribió
我认为是在1月21日我们玩的是，在1月19日，这将是我祖母的生日。
I think it was on January 21 that we played and on January 19 it would be my grandmother's birthday.
Creo que fue el 21 de enero que jugábamos y el 19 de enero sería el cumpleaños de mi abuela.
我总是说当我到达曼彻斯特和这里时，我选择了19
that I always say that I chose 19 when I arrive at Manchester and here for
que siempre digo que el elegí el 19 cuando llegue al Manchester y acá por
在我祖母的生日那天，我们在家生活了很多时间。
For my grandmother's birthday, that we lived a lot of time at home.
Por el cumpleaños de mi abuela, que nosotros vivimos mucho tiempo en su casa.
这是一个非常重要的人。
It was a very important person.
Fue una persona muy importante.
他告诉我，那天母亲写信给我，今天是一个致力于天堂的目标。
And he told me, the mother wrote to me that day, today a goal dedicated to heaven and that is made.
Y me dijo, me escribió el mamá ese día, hoy se hace un gol dedicado al cielo y eso.
前几天，我不认识母亲的祖父，但她也在比赛前给我发了一条消息。
And the other day, I did not know my grandfather from my mother, but she also sent me a message before the game.
Y el otro día, yo no conocía a mi abuelo de parte de mi mamá, pero también ella me mandó un mensaje antes del partido.
如果您实现了一个目标，他今天就把我放了...您没有遇到他...
And he put me today if you made a goal you didn't meet him ...
y me puso hoy si hacés un gol no lo conociste a...
对于你的祖父，我本来比他的生活更爱你，你和你的兄弟，我知道，那我把它献给了，因为我的母亲
To your grandfather, but I would have loved you more than his life, you and your brothers and that I know, then well, I dedicated it to that because my mother
a tu abuelo, pero te hubiese querido más que a su vida, a vos y a tus hermanos y que sé yo, entonces bueno, lo dediqué por eso porque mi mamá
我没有告诉我。
I hadn't told me that.
No me había dicho eso.
这是一个美丽的故事，仍然与梅西（Messi）相似，因为梅西（Messi）的庆祝活动也是祖母。
It is a beautiful story and still has a parallel with Messi because Messi's celebration is also the grandmother.
Es una linda historia y sigue teniendo un paralelismo con Messi porque el festejo de Messi es por la abuela también.
那是献给她的，也说话
that is dedicated to her and that also speaks
que se lo dedica a ella y eso habla también
全家人做出很多牺牲的人，对您很重要，您可以实现一百个目标。
People beyond the whole family who make a lot of sacrifice, who are important to you, that you can, you can make a hundred goals.
las personas más allá de toda la familia que hacen mucho sacrificio, que son importantes para ustedes, que ustedes pueden, vos podés hacer cien goles.
但是，在这种情况下，您的祖母或您的家人或不为您改变任何事情的人，因此您的生活将永远改变。
But your grandmother, in this case, or your family, or the people who do not change anything for you, so your life changes forever.
pero tu abuela, en este caso, o tu familia, o las personas que para ustedes no cambian nada, así su vida cambie para siempre.
是的，好吧，祖父母，父母显然是非常重要的人。
Yes, well, grandparents, parents are obviously very important people.
Sí, bueno, los abuelos, los padres obviamente son personas muy importantes.
正如我的祖母告诉你的那样，我有一个仍在阿根廷的人。
As my grandmother told you, I have one that is still in Argentina.
Como te dije mi abuela, tengo una que todavía está en Argentina.
但是几年前去世的人，正如我说的那样
But the one who died a few years ago, as I said we lived before at home
pero sí la que falleció hace unos años, nosotros como dije antes vivimos en su casa
好吧，自从我出生以来，我们和她一起住在家里。
Well, since I was born that we live with her at home.
Bueno, desde que yo nací que vivimos con ella en su casa.
我认为我父亲已经走了六个月，因为那是家庭的糟糕时期，我们留下了...
I think my dad had gone for six months because it was a bad time of the family and we stayed ...
Creo que mi papá había ido por seis meses porque fue una mala época de la familia y nos quedamos...
在那里二十年，我们甚至继续在​​那所房子里，所以这就是为什么。
As twenty years there, well, we even continue in that house, so that's why it was.
como veinte años ahí, bueno, hasta seguimos en esa casa, así que por eso fue.
这就是为什么谢谢。
And that's why thanks.
Y por eso el agradecimiento.
你按自己吗？
Do you press yourself?
¿Vos te presionás a vos mismo?
因为如果您看到自己的电话号码，我现在就不会把它们拿出来，因为我没有太多的时间张贴并离开。
Because if you see your numbers, I'm not going to get them out now because I don't have so much time for a note and leave.
Porque si ves tus números, no los voy a sacar ahora porque tampoco tengo tanto tiempo de nota y se me va largo.
但是当朱利安说他真的赢得了第一位赢得了自由主义者冠军的球员
But when Julián said he really won the first player who won Premier Libertadores Champions
pero cuando dicen Julián ganó todo y de verdad el primer jugador que ganó Champions Premier Libertadores
这会向您移动某些东西还是对您的统计数据？
Does that move something to you or is it a statistic for you?
¿eso a vos te mueve algo o es una estadística para vos?
不，让我们看看它是否很好，这是一个梦。
No, let's see if it's something nice, it's a dream.
No, a ver si que es algo lindo, que es un sueño.
即使是赢得冠军或其他任何玩家，这也是某些玩家梦dream以求的事情。
It is something that some players dream of, even if it is to win a title or whatever.
Es algo que algunos jugadores sueñan con, aunque sea ganar un título o lo que sea.
对我来说，随着这个年龄的增长，他们都给了我那样，大多数人，最重要的是。
And to me, with this age, that they have all given me like that, most, all the most important.
Y a mí, con esta edad, que se me hayan dado todos así, la mayoría, todos los más importantes.
非常好的事物很疯狂，但我试图传播
Something very nice is crazy but well I try to spread
algo muy lindo es loco pero bueno trato de difundir
虽然不在那里，但我不停地认为发生的一切，而且很多事情经常来了，这真是太好了。
While not there I do not stop to think everything that happened and many things are very often come, it is something nice.
Si bien no por ahí no me detengo a pensar todo lo que pasó y se vienen muchas cosas muy seguidas, sí que es algo lindo.
朱利安，为什么在这里和城市里没有那么多？
Julian, why here and in the City not so much?
Julián, ¿por qué acá sí y en el City no tanto?
我不会说不是因为他们在网站上有三胞胎。
I will not say not because they have a triplet on the site.
No voy a decir no porque me tienen un triplete en el sitio.
什么在这个城市更舒适？
What is more comfortable in this city?
¿Qué es que está más cómodo en esta ciudad?
是技术人员吗？
Is the technician?
¿Es el técnico?
有些事情失败了吗？
Did something fail?
¿Falló algo?
不，不，自从我到达以来的城市中的真相，好吧...
No, no, the truth that in the City since I arrived, well ...
No, no, la verdad que en el City desde que llegué, bueno...
首先，他们信任我，他们从河到欧洲，我打了很多游戏，我实现了许多目标，我们赢得了冠军。
First they trusted me, they brought me from River to Europe, I played a lot of games, I made many goals, we won titles.
Primero confiaron en mí, me trajeron de River a Europa, jugué un montón de partidos, hice muchos goles, ganamos títulos.
那是完美的，如果我继续那里，我也会很舒服，我总是说我是
That was perfect and if I had continued there I would have also been comfortable, I always said that I am
eso fue perfecto y si hubiese seguido ahí también hubiese estado cómoda siempre dije que estoy
非常感谢俱乐部，但我确实需要一些东西告诉我，我需要一个不同的挑战才能寻找新的东西
Very grateful to the club but I did need something inside mine told me that I needed a different challenge to look for something new that
muy agradecido al club pero sí que necesitaba algo algo dentro mío me decía que necesitaba un desafío diferente buscar algo nuevo que
没有动力，因为我总是想继续更多的事情，但是
no motivation because I will always want to continue for more but something that
no motivación porque siempre voy a querer seguir por más pero si algo que
我职业生涯中的一个不同的挑战，我觉得这可能是我的住所。
A different challenge in my career and I felt that here could be my place for ...
Un reto diferente en mi carrera y sentí que acá podía ser mi lugar para...
为了更好地，要找到我作为足球运动员最好的版本，那就有点了。
To develop better, to find my best version as a footballer, then it was a bit for that.
para desarrollarme mejor, para encontrar mi mejor versión como futbolista, entonces fue un poco por eso.
但是你在那里度过了糟糕的时光吗？
But did you have a bad time there?
¿Pero la pasaste mal ahí?
不，不，事实不是。
No, no, the truth is not.
No, no, la verdad que no.
是的，正如我所说，那里的人想玩最重要的游戏。
Yes, one out there wants to play the most important games, as I said.
Sí que uno por ahí quiere jugar los partidos más importantes, como dije.
在冠军联赛决赛中，我没有进入半决赛并打了一点时间。
In the Champions League final, I did not enter the semifinal and played a little time.
en la final del Champions, no entré en la semifinal y jugué poco tiempo.
时间和这样的比赛，我不想玩。
time and such matches and that I would not have liked to play them.
tiempo y ese tipo de partidos y que no hubiese gustado jugarlos.
但是什么都没有，这就是他之前说的原因。
But nothing, a little that's why he said before.
Pero nada, un poco por eso que decía antes.
但是我想改变。
But I think about change.
Pero pienso en el cambio.
我看到了亚特塞托（Atlético）总统的陈述说...
I saw statements from Atlético President saying ...
Yo vi declaraciones del presidente del Atlético diciendo...
因为一开始它花费了改编。
because in the beginning it cost the adaptation.
porque en el principio costó la adaptación.
不幸的是，每个人都希望朱利安每场比赛能实现三个进球。
Unfortunately everyone expects Julian to make three goals per game.
Lamentablemente todos esperan que Julián haga tres goles por partido.
对于任何人来说，这几乎是不可能的。
That is almost impossible for anyone.
Eso es casi imposible para nadie.
他说我带他了，因为我想要，并且因为他是世界冠军。
He said I brought him because I want and because he is the world champion.
Dijo lo traje porque quiero y porque es el campeón del mundo.
还有cholo ...
And the cholo ...
Y el Cholo...
西蒙内（Simeone）几乎在这里生活了，这实际上就是这个俱乐部。
Simeone, who has almost a life here is practically this club.
Simeone, que tiene casi una vida acá prácticamente es este club.
他说，他是给我带来最大幻想的球员。
He said, he's the player who brought me the most illusion.
dijo, es el jugador que trajimos que más ilusión me hizo.
所以...
So...
Entonces...
我想您会得到我在这里说的那家银行，我想要它，我将全部储蓄。
I imagine that you get that bank that I say here, I want it and I will bank it in all.
Imagino que a vos te llega esa banca que como que acá digan, lo quiero y lo voy a bancar en todas.
是的，从第一时刻开始，人民的爱，到达俱乐部，...
Yes, from the first moment, the love of the people, reach the club and ...
Sí, desde el primer momento, el cariño de la gente, llegar al club y...
并看到所有去体育场接受我们所有人的人。
and see all the people who went to the stadium to receive us all.
y ver toda la gente que fue al Estadio a recibirnos a todos.
我几乎没有到达机场，所有人在飞行后都在那里。
I barely arrived at the airport, all the people were there following the flight and that.
Apenas llegué al aeropuerto, estaba toda la gente ahí siguiendo el vuelo y eso.
这让我感到非常重要，然后我试图证明这一点。
It makes me feel very important and then I try to prove it.
Me hace sentir muy importante y después trato de demostrarlo.
在球场上，乔也在奥林匹克运动会前与我交谈时，也是如此
On the court, Cholo also when he talked to me the days before there at the Olympic Games and those days also
en la cancha, el Cholo también cuando me hablaba los días previos ahí en los Juegos Olímpicos y esos días también me
他说服了我，他告诉了我很多俱乐部的事情，而不仅仅是...
He convinced me, he told me a lot of things from the club, not just for ...
me convenció, me dijo un montón de cosas del club, no solo para...
现在，但是在未来几年。
For now, but in the coming years.
para ahora, sino en los años que vienen.
好吧，我喜欢它。
And well, I liked that.
Y bueno, eso me gustó.
是的，你知道。
Yes, you know perfectly.
Sí, lo sabes perfecto.
阿根廷人在阿根廷人的任何地方都在阿根廷人那里。
There the Argentines bank to the Argentines in whatever.
Allá los argentinos bancamos a los argentinos en lo que sea.
特别是阿根廷队的举动
particularly the Argentine team move
particularmente la selección argentina mueve masas pero claro en su momento hubo una declaración de Guardiola que no gustó, allá se picó
同时，瓜迪奥拉（Guardiola）在狮子座（Leo）的舞台上爱他，但随后您会有这种对比。
At the same time, Guardiola loves him by Leo's stage, but then you have this contrast.
a la vez a Guardiola se lo quiere por la etapa de Leo, pero después tenés este contraste.
Simeone说他们正在和所有人在一起。
Simeone saying that they are going with everyone.
Simeone diciendo que lo van con todas.
埃斯卡洛尼（Escaloni）最近在接受采访时说，朱利安（Julian）想要任何技术人员。
Escaloni recently in an interview said that Julian wants any technician.
Escaloni hace poco en una entrevista dijo que Julián lo quiere cualquier técnico.
这些陈述会给您吗？
Do these statements get to you?
¿A vos te llegan esas declaraciones?
你是职责。
You are duties.
Vos sos deberes.
我不知道，您发送消息。
I don't know, you send a message.
No sé, mandás un mensaje.
想象一下楼梯。
Imagine staircase.
Imagino a Scaloni.
切，谢谢。
Che, thanks.
Che, gracias.
我不知道你怎么告诉狮子座。
I don't know how you tell Leo.
No sé cómo le decís a Leo.
我不是发送消息，但我确实看到了。
I am not sending messages, but I do see it.
No soy de mandar así mensajes, pero sí que lo veo.
我对我的所有技术人员都很好，实际上，还有什么...
All the technicians I had treated me very well, in fact there is more than what ...
Todos los técnicos que tuve me han tratado muy bien, de hecho por ahí se dice más de lo que...
到底是什么，我与Pep的最后一次对话是...
What really is, the last conversations I had with PEP were ...
Lo que realmente es, las últimas conversaciones que tuve con Pep fueron...
非常感谢您两年来给我们提供的一切，有很多头衔，您从来没有做过任何问题，您没有带任何...
Thank you very much for everything you gave us in two years, there were many titles, you never did any problem, you did not bring any ...
Muchas gracias por todo lo que nos diste en dos años, fueron muchísimos títulos, nunca hiciste ningún problema, no trajiste ningún...
没有俱乐部中的Quilombo，什么都没有，您总是给您最大的，而不是投诉，所以他们总是如此。
Not a quilombo in the club, nothing, you always give you to the maximum, not a complaint, so they always were.
ni un quilombo en el club, nada, siempre te brindas hasta el máximo, ni una queja, así que siempre fueron.
感谢俱乐部的感谢和我的话。
Words of thanks and mine to the club too.
Palabras de agradecimiento y mías hacia el club también.
从选择中，我想我告诉了恩佐，或者我不记得那是恩佐。
From the selection, I think I told Enzo, or I don't remember if it was Enzo.
de la selección, esto creo que lo contó Enzo, o no me acuerdo si fue Enzo.
因为一件事是跳入邦迪，我了解你。
Because one thing is to jump in the bondi, I understand you.
Porque una cosa es saltar en el bondi, te lo entiendo.
你乘直升机跳了吗？
Did you jump by helicopter?
¿Saltaste en helicóptero?
不，我记得我们在那里。
Jump no, but we were there, I remember.
Saltar no, pero sí estábamos ahí, me acuerdo.
好吧，我们之所以服用了一点，因为它很热，必须水合。
Well, we had taken a little because it was very hot and it had to be hydrated.
Y bueno, un poco habíamos tomado porque hacía mucho calor y había que hidratarse.
切碎，切碎。
It was chopped, a little chopped.
Estaba picado, un poquito picado.
有一个视频，您看到了。
There is a video, you saw it.
Hay un video, lo viste.
我和我们在一起。
I was the coach there with us.
Estaba el técnico ahí con nosotros.
伊斯特帕拉（Easterpala）的Colomacal。
Colomacal, Easterpala, there.
Colomacal, Easterpala, ahí.
没什么，我们他妈的是因为他们有一些恐惧。
And nothing, we moved fucking because they had some some fear.
Y nada, nos movíamos jodiendo porque tenían algunos un poco de miedo.
直升机正在关注他，我们演奏了他在这里移动，搬到那里的方式。
The helicopter was paying attention to him and we played how he moves here, moves there, that kind of thing.
Le daba caso el helicóptero y nosotros jugábamos como se mueve para acá, se mueve para allá, ese tipo de cosas.
也就是说，有楼梯乐队。
That is, there is the Staircase Band.
O sea, ahí está la banda de la escaloneta.
它在这里移动，移动到那里。
It moves here, moves there.
Se mueve para acá, se mueve para allá.
向上直升机。
Up the helicopter.
Arriba el helicóptero.
玩。
played.
jugado.
不，但是很少，那里很短。
No, but little, there short.
No, pero poquito, ahí cortito.
我记得卡洛尼现在告诉我说话。
And I remember that Caloni told me now to speak.
Y recuerdo que ahí Caloni me dijo ahora hablar.
当他试图害羞而宽松时。
As he tried to be shy and there was loose.
Como que te trató de tímido y ahí estaba suelto.
更松散。
A little more loose.
Un poco más suelto.
好吧，但是你是科尔多瓦。
Well, but you are Cordoba.
Bueno, pero vos sos cordobés.
蕨类植物在成为世界冠军之后可能会悄悄与蕨类植物在一起。
And the Fernet when he can, after being world champion, can quietly be with the Fernet.
Y el Fernet cuando puede, después de ser campeón del mundo, tranquilamente puede estar con los Fernet.
超出应有的。
More than deserved.
Más que merecido.
“如果你吉斯河？”
"If you guise River?"
¿Se guisa River?
是的，是的。
Yes, yes.
Sí, sí.
我试图看他。
I try to look at him.
Trato de mirarlo.
有时间表。
There is a schedule.
Hay un desfasaje horario.
是的，昨晚有点晚了，但是如果没有，我会尝试看他。
Yes, last night it was a bit late, but if not, I try to look at him.
Sí, anoche fue un poco tarde, pero si no, trato de mirarlo.
你看到了。
You see it.
Lo ves.
人们问你，但你刚离开。
People ask you, but you just left.
La gente te pide, pero recién te fuiste.
你看到发生了什么吗？
Did you see what happens?
¿Viste qué pasa eso?
Chabon在欧洲是一年，他们已经希望您返回。
The chabon is a year in Europe and they already want you to return.
El chabón está un año en Europa y ya quieren que vuelvas.
那将永远发生，您是有意识的。
That will happen forever and you are conscious.
Eso va a pasar para siempre y sos consciente.
是的，我知道在阿根廷意味着什么人。
Yes, I know what people, which means in Argentina.
Sí, sé lo que la gente, lo que significa en Argentina.
我知道这有点坚持，因为我很少我在这里。
I know it's a bit insists because I am little that I'm here.
Sé que es un poco insiste porque hace poquito que estoy acá.
最新的，你的家人...
The latest, your family ...
Lo último, tu familia...
他们刚刚做了很大的努力，就像您刚刚做的那样，但与此同时
They have made a very big effort, of kids, as you just had, but at the same time
han hecho un esfuerzo muy grande, de pibes, como recién contabas, pero a la vez
它表明这是一个非常简单，非常谦虚的家庭。
It shows that it is a very simple, very humble family.
Se nota que es una familia muy sencilla, muy humilde.
还有一个视频是两三年的历史，这是您离开的时候。
There is also a video that is two or three years old, which is when you leave.
Hay un video también que tiene dos o tres años, que es cuando vos te vas.
这就像他们向任何旅行的普通人说再见，这样的事情。
That is like they are saying goodbye to any common person who goes on a trip returned, such a thing.
que es como que están despidiendo a cualquier persona común que se va de viaje regresado, una cosa así.
这很好，我想这会让您拥有这些价值观，您是一个安静的孩子，您是一个简单，谦虚的孩子。
And that is nice, I imagine that makes you have these values, that you are a quiet kid, that you are a simple, humble kid.
Y eso es lindo, imagino que eso hace que vos tengas estos valores, que seas un pibe tranquilo, que seas un pibe sencillo, humilde.
是的，总是非常感谢我的老年人，好吧，我的兄弟们年纪大了，已经标记了一条道路。
Yes, always very grateful to my old people, well, my brothers who are older and have marked a path.
Sí, siempre muy agradecido a mis viejos, bueno, a mis hermanos también que son más grandes y me han marcado un camino.
他们从很小的时候就对我来说就是一个例子。
They are an example for me from a very young age.
Son un ejemplo para mí desde muy chico.
我们总是这样去，一家人...
We always went like this, the family ...
Siempre fuimos así, la familia...
非常接近我的兄弟们。
Very close to my brothers.
muy unida con mis hermanos.
我的老人没有错过任何比赛，他们将我们带到到处，任何比赛，所有比赛，周六，周日。
My old men did not miss any game, they took us everywhere, any tournament, all games, Saturdays, on Sundays.
Mis viejos no se perdían ningún partido, nos llevaban a todos lados, cualquier torneo, todos los partidos, los sábados, los domingos.
在镇上，我们从未失踪过，他们总是陪伴我们。
There in the town, we were never missing, they were always accompanying us.
ahí en el pueblo, nos faltaban nunca, estuvieron siempre acompañándonos.
所以今天他们在这里陪着我。
So today they accompany me here.
Así que hoy en día me acompañan acá.
他们不想错过任何游戏，因为他们总是这样做。
They don't want to miss any game, because they always did so.
No se quieren perder ningún partido, porque lo hicieron siempre así.
因此，对我来说，他们今天可以生活是一种骄傲。
So for me it is a pride that they can live today.
Entonces para mí es un orgullo que puedan vivir hoy.
今天，当我们是男人时，我们实现了梦想。
Today, the dream we had when we were guys.
Hoy en día, el sueño que teníamos de cuando éramos chicos.
作为男朋友，你多久了？
And as a boyfriend how long are you?
¿Y de novio hace cuánto tiempo estás?
两年前的男友在八月份，差不多三个。
Boyfriend two years ago and a little, almost three in August.
De novio hace dos años y un poco, casi tres en agosto.
是的。
Yeah.
Sí.
也是我去曼彻斯特的时候。
It was also when I was going to Manchester.
También fue cuando me iba para Manchester.
我们彼此认识男孩。
And we know each other as boys.
y nos conocemos de chicos.
她的父亲来自卡尔钦镇。
Her father is from the town of Calchín.
El padre de ella es del pueblo de Calchín.
我的祖父一直是我的老朋友，她的祖父住在镇上，然后...
Always my old very friend of the dad, her grandfather lived in the town, then ...
Siempre mi viejo muy amigo del papá, el abuelo de ella vivía en el pueblo, entonces...
它会在那里，我们知道自己是10岁，但是嘿，直到最近才发生。
It was going to be there, we know ourselves as 10 years old, but hey, it had not occurred until recently.
Iba a ser ahí, nos conocemos como de los 10 años, pero bueno, no se había dado hasta hace poco.
你面对还是他们面对？
Did you face or were they faced?
¿Vos encaraste o te encararon?
不，因为如果您以前认识她，而一无所有...
No, because if you knew her before and nothing ...
No, porque si la conocías de antes y nada...
它很小，也许我开始了，然后是她的舞台。
It was very small, maybe I started, then a stage that she.
Fue muy de chico, quizás empecé yo, después una etapa que ella.
我们总是有...
We always had ...
Siempre tuvimos...
从10到现在，总是有这样的东西给人太多，有时候我有时，有时她有点。
From 10 until now there was always like that that gives so much, a little sometimes me, a little sometimes she.
Desde los 10 hasta ahora siempre hubo así encontronazo que da tanto, un poco a veces yo, un poco a veces ella.
真是太好了...我已经离开了这里。
How nice to have ... I already get out of here.
Qué lindo tener... Ya salgo de acá.
有一个生活伴侣真是太好了。
How nice to have a life partner.
Qué lindo tener una compañera de vida.
因为毕竟，我们前一段时间说的
Because after all, what we say a while ago,
Porque al fin y al cabo, en lo que decimos hace un rato,
他们在这里，您必须一直训练。
They are here and you have to train all the time.
están acá y vos tenés que entrenar todo el tiempo.
他们也不在度假或关闭。
Nor is they on vacation or close.
Tampoco es que están de vacaciones ni cerca.
不，显然，对她非常感激，因为他们必须做很多事情。
No, obviously, very grateful to her because they have to go with a lot of things.
No, obviamente, muy agradecido con ella porque tienen que van con un montón de cosas.
按照我们的日程安排来适应您的生活，将自己置于末日的一天，一天的早晨，我们旅行的一天，那个季前赛。
Accommodate your life according to our schedules, put ourselves in a day in the late plot, one day in the morning that we travel, that preseason.
acomodar su vida de acuerdo a nuestros horarios, ponernos en un día en trama tarde, un día en la mañana que viajamos, que pretemporada.
这一切总是在做饭，清洁。
That this and well, is always cooking, cleaning.
que esto y bueno, ya está siempre cocinando, limpiando.
在糟糕的时期，享受美好时光，所以非常感激。
Banking at bad times, enjoying good times, so it is very grateful.
bancando en los malos momentos, disfrutando de los buenos todo el tiempo, así que es muy agradecido.
这称为史诗。
This is called the epic.
Esto se llama la épica.
我们在阿根廷国家队历史上选择了重要时刻。
We chose important moments at our criteria in the history of the Argentine National Team.
Nosotros elegimos momentos importantes a nuestro criterio de la historia de la selección argentina.
而且您必须选择最喜欢哪个。
And you have to choose which one you like best.
y vos tenés que elegir cuál te gusta más.
他考虑到，在给您的两个人中，您选择的一张票是半决赛，然后是决赛，就像世界杯一样。
He contemplates that, of the two that puts you, the one you choose passes to Semi and then is the final and goes like a World Cup.
Contempla que, de los dos que te ponga, el que elegís pasa a semi y después es la final y va como un mundial.
是的。
Yeah.
Sí.
我可以开始吗？
Can I start?
¿Puedo arrancar?
是的？
Yeah?
¿Sí?
戴尔，戴尔。
Dale, dale.
让我们看看，让我们看看。
Let's see, let's see.
A ver, vamos a ver.
是还是不是？
Yes or no?
¿Sí o no?
我开始。
I start.
Arranco.
这很困难。
This is difficult.
Esto es difícil.
这很困难。
This is difficult.
Esto es difícil.
我不喜欢做出决定。
I don't like making decisions.
No me gusta así tomar decisiones.
最终使用说的星号，这让我很遗憾，我说，我不编辑它。
Finally use the asterisk of saying, it makes me pity and I put that, I do not edit it.
de última usa el asterisco de decir, me da lástima y yo te pongo eso, no lo edito.
不，所以你不会留下来...什么都没有，我要选择。
No, so you don't stay like ... nothing, I'm going to choose.
No, para que no quedes como... Nada, voy a elegir.
好吧，去。
Well, go.
Bueno, va.
抽签的狂欢。
THE SCRESS OF THE DRAW.
La atajada del Dibu.
第94-95分钟还是迭戈的目标还是英语？
Minute 94-95 or Diego's goal or the English?
¿Minuto 94-95 o el gol de Diego o los ingleses?
没有什么困难。
Nothing is difficult.
Nada, es difícil.
是的。
Yeah.
Sí.
但是儿子是德国，因为我在那里。
But the son was the DER because I was there.
Pero el hijo era el Dibu porque estuve ahí.
然后，我们的问候，如果没有，又一Chao，Chao。
And us greetings, then, if not, Chao, Chao.
Y nos saludos, pues, si no, chao, chao.
不，不。
No no.
No, no.
这很漂亮。
This is beautiful.
Esto es hermoso.
阿根廷世界冠军的burruchaga的目标，或...
The goal of Burruchaga, Argentina world champion, or ...
El gol de Burruchaga, Argentina campeona del mundo, o...
您的目标...那是杂技，对吗？
Your goal ... is that acrobatics, right?
Tu gol... ¿Ese es Acrobacia, no?
是的，杂技。
Yes, acrobatics.
Sí, Acrobacia.
它不是第一个，不是apoloña。
It is not the first, it is not Apoloña.
No es el primero, no es Apoloña.
我们不久前谈论的那个。
The one we talked about a while ago.
El que hablamos hace un rato.
是的！
Yeah!
¡Sí!
不，我保留。
No, I keep that.
No, me quedo con ese.
我只是说我是，但是我必须选择这一点，因为那是决赛。
I just said I was, but I have to choose that because it was the final.
Recién dije que estuve yo, pero tengo que elegir ese porque fue la final.
但是在这里，您没有看到您来自法院的一半。
But here you didn't see that you came from half of the court.
Pero acá no viste que venías de la mitad de la cancha.
也就是说，您必须看到视频。
That is, you have to see the video back.
O sea, vos tenés que ver el video de vuelta.
你走了一次。
You came walking once.
Venías caminando una vez.
但是我们以3-0赢了，然后进球较少...
But we won 3-0 that, then with a goal less ...
Pero ganamos 3-0 ese, entonces con un gol menos…
我们走到最后。
We went to the end the same.
Pasábamos al final igual.
好吧，准备好，完美。
Well, ready, perfect.
Bueno, que listo, perfecto.
狮子座对墨西哥的进球，这是你的伴侣，使他赢得了世界冠军。
Leo's goal to Mexico, this a partner of yours made him winner, world champion.
El gol de Leo a México, este un compañero tuyo lo hizo ganador, campeón del mundo.
El庆祝班加尔。
El celebrates the Bangal.
O el festejo a Bangal.
它来自墨西哥。
It is from Mexico.
Es de México.
这是每个人都告诉我的，他们感到很多，对吗？
This, for what everyone has been telling me, they felt a lot, right?
Esto, por lo que me vienen diciendo todos, lo sintieron muchísimo, ¿no?
此外，我认为它也可能赢了。
Moreover, I think it may be that it wins too.
Es más, yo creo que puede ser que gane también.
Desagobo总数。
Desagobo total.
是的。
Yeah.
Sí.
我一生中的一刻，我不知道，至关重要。
A moment of my life, I don't know, crucial.
Un momento de mi vida, no sé, crucial.
银行上的狗屎。
A shit on the bank.
Un cagazo en el banco.
然后我已经进入了游戏，但是上半场以及所有这些...
Then I had already entered the game, but the first half and all that ...
Después ya había entrado en el partido, pero el primer tiempo y todo eso...
与墨西哥的比赛的那几分钟太糟糕了。
Those minutes of the match against Mexico were terrible.
Esos minutos del partido contra México fueron terribles.
玛丽亚不给狮子座的通行证。
Maria does not give Leo's pass.
María no le da el pase a Leo.
到目前为止，他们从未遭受过痛苦。
So far they were suffering as never.
Hasta ahí estaban sufriendo como nunca.
好吧，你的伴侣告诉我。
Well, a partner of yours told me.
Bueno, me lo dijo un compañero tuyo.
他告诉我有关波尔的事。
He told me about Pol.
Me lo dijo de Pol.
是的，不，对我来说...好吧，准备好，我要通过它。
Yes, no, for me ... well, ready, I'm going to pass it.
Sí, no, para mí... Bueno, listo, lo voy a hacer pasar.
最后，迭戈（Diego）的目标是英国人的目标，还是Cachete Montiel的目标使您成为世界冠军？
In the end, does Diego's goal to the English or the goal of Cachete Montiel make you world champion?
Al final, ¿el gol de Diego a los ingleses o el gol de Cachete Montiel te hace campeón del mundo?
今天你有25岁，但是你在这里有什么？
Today you have 25, but what did you have here?
Hoy tenés 25, pero ¿qué tenías acá?
¿23？
¿23?
€24？
¿24?
在那里，22。
There, 22.
Ahí, 22.
你看到了，我告诉你，22。
You saw, I told you, 22.
Viste, te dije, 22.
有22年。
With 22 years.
Con 22 años.
嗯...
Eh...
而且在这里您说我无法犯错，您很有信心。
And also that here you said that I could not err, that you were confident.
Y además que acá dijiste que no lo podía errar, que confiabas.
但是在这里，您看到了英语，它给了它，它运行，接受...
But here you saw the English, it gives it, it runs, take ...
Pero acá viste que se la inglese, se la da, se va corriendo, toma...
所以后来，你看到了。
So later, you saw.
así después, viste.
他做了什么？
What did he do?
¿Qué hizo?
作为？
As?
¿Cómo?
不，不，但是我不喜欢它。
No, no, but I don't like it.
No, no, pero no me gusta.
您的第一阶段告诉您我怎么能，Álvarez。
Your first stage tells you how I can, Álvarez.
Tu primera etapa le dice cómo puedo, Álvarez.
我们走了脸，但我的灵魂很痛。
We go cheeking, but my soul hurts.
Vamos con cachete, pero me duele el alma.
但是，我们和Cachi一起去。
But well, we go with Cachi.
Pero bueno, vamos con Cachi.
让我们去这里。
Let's go here.
Vamos acá.
给它，完美。
Give it, perfect.
Dale, perfecto.
好吧，看。
Well, look.
Bueno, mira.
在这里，最后一个通行证。
And here the final passes.
Y acá pasa la final.
布鲁鲁目标的切片？
The slice of the Burrú goal?
¿La tajada del Dibu o el gol de Burrú?
抽奖。
The Draw.
El DIBU.
平局，完美。
The draw, perfect.
El DIBU, perfecto.
另一个半是...
The other semi is ...
La otra semi es...
狮子座的bochazo。
Leo's bochazo.
El bochazo de Leo.
哦，看看这两个时刻。
Oh, look at these two moments.
Ah, mirá estos dos momentos.
狮子座的bochazo。
Leo's bochazo.
El bochazo de Leo.
§是吗？
§ is it?
¿Este?
哪个世界冠军？
Which world champion?
¿A qué campeón del mundo?
第二场世界杯比赛。
This second World Cup match.
Este segundo partido del Mundial de 7.
是的，但是我们没有到达那里。
Yes, but we didn't get there.
Sí, pero no llegábamos ahí.
没有机会。
There was no chance.
No había chance.
最终的。
Final.
Bochazo de Leo到墨西哥，第二场比赛。
Bochazo de Leo to Mexico, second game.
Bochazo de Leo a México, segundo partido.
或绘画中的配音。
Or the dub from drawing.
O la tajada del Dibu.
这两个钥匙在决赛中，但我坚持下去。
The two keys are in the final, but I stay with that.
Las dos claves están en la final, pero me quedo con esa.
我的墨西哥球。
My Mexican ball.
Mi bola mexicana.
这是我们带来的史诗般的胜利。
This is the one that wins for you the epic that we brought.
Esto es el que gana para vos la épica que nosotros trajimos.
是的，是的。
Yes, yes.
Sí, sí.
大喊大叫的目标之一。
One of the most shouted goals.
Uno de los goles más gritados.
我相信世界杯。
Of the World Cup, I believe.
Del Mundial, yo creo.
是的，是的。
Yes, yes.
Sí, sí.
在这个目标中，Gio的女儿出生了。
To, in this goal, Gio's daughter was born.
Para, en este gol, nació la hija de Gio.
你知道吗？
Did you know that, right?
¿Sabías eso, no?
是的，他打破了6，就在那里。
Yes, he broke the 6 and that, right there.
Sí, que rompió el 6 y eso, justo ahí.
听我说，我有一个问题。
Listen to me, I have a question.
Escúchame, tengo una pregunta.
我今天在法庭上。
I was on the court this day.
Yo estaba en la cancha este día.
我要告诉你这种感觉。
I'm going to tell you this feeling.
Te voy a contar esta sensación.
我听到了沉默和足球从法庭上听到的。
And I heard like a silence and football was heard from the court.
Y yo escuché como un silencio y desde la cancha se escuchó el fútbol.
听到了直到Bochazo击中他以及他进入时。
It was heard until when the bochazo hit him and when he enters.
Se escuchó hasta cuando le pega el bochazo y cuando entra.
你里面，你感觉到什么？
You inside, what did you feel?
Vos adentro, ¿qué sentiste?
不，这是一个目标，目标。
No, it was a goal on top, goal.
No, fue un golazo encima, golazo.
好吧，正如我所说的，我在里面，我已经进入了。
Well, as I said just, I was inside, I had already entered.
Bueno, ahí como dije recién, estaba adentro, ya había entrado.
从外面他遭受的痛苦更多，但是在那里...
From outside he suffers much more, but there ...
De afuera se sufre mucho más, pero ahí...
我认为达​​到峰，看看我是否把它交给了我，但它击中了拱门。
I think peak to see if I gave it to me, but less bad that it hit the arch.
Yo creo que pico para ver si me la daba, pero menos mal que le pegó al arco.
看看它是否给您责任，对吗？
Look if it gives you responsibility, right?
Mira si te da la responsabilidad, ¿no?
不，不。
No no.
No, no.
这是吗？
Is this?
¿Queda este?
这是吗？
Is this?
¿Queda este?
是的，是的。
Yes, yes.
Sí, sí.
好吧，恭喜。
Well, congratulations.
Bueno, felicitaciones.
我们带来了筹码。
We brought chips.
Nosotros trajimos fichas.
这是象征性的，因为这是银。
This is symbolic because this acts as silver.
Esto es simbólico porque esto hace a las veces de plata.
钱，好吗？
Of money, okay?
de dinero, ¿está bien?
我们要尝试的...不，好，也没有那么多。
What we are going to try ... No, well, there is not so much either.
Nosotros lo que vamos a intentar... No, bueno, tampoco hay tanto.
我们要尝试的是为您购买世界杯的最后衬衫。
What we are going to try is to buy you the final shirt of the World Cup.
Lo que vamos a intentar es comprarte la camiseta de final de la Copa del Mundo.
你有衬衫吗？
Do you have your shirt?
¿Vos tenés tu camiseta?
一两个。
One or two.
Uno o dos.
的。
Of the.
Dos.
你们都有吗？
Do you all have you?
¿Todas las tenés vos?
是的。
Yeah.
Sí.
像每个人一样，直到上半场或下半场都没有人发布。
Like everyone, no one released one until the first half or second half.
Como todos, nadie liberó una hasta el primer tiempo o el segundo tiempo.
是的，我都有。
Yes, I have both.
Sí, tengo las dos.
好的。
GOOD.
Bien.
我可以...很糟糕，我三岁，我想。
I can ... it's bad, I'm three, I think.
Te puedo... Es mal, tengo tres, creo.
三岁？
How three?
¿Cómo tres?
只是不可能。
It just can't be.
No puede ser.
不，我知道，但是有些事情……发生了...
No, I know, but something very ... happened ...
No, yo sé, pero pasó algo muy...
很疯狂。
Very crazy that it was.
Muy loco que fue.
如果您看到照片，我是唯一一个带着天体潜水员出去的人。
If you see the photo, I am the only one who goes out with a celestial diver.
Si vos veis la foto, soy el único que salgo con buzo celeste.
他们都穿着衬衫。
And they are all with the shirt.
y están todos con la camiseta.
当我离开它时，我把它留在这里，然后放了潜水员。
When I left it, I left it here and I put the diver.
Yo cuando salí me la saqué, la dejo acá y me pongo el buzo.
一切都湿了。
It was all wet.
Estaba toda mojada.
没什么，我要去庆祝活动，我们都庆祝并告诉马里托，切玛丽托...
And nothing, I'm going to the celebrations, we all celebrate and tell Marito, Che Marito ...
Y nada, me voy a los festejos, festejamos todos y le digo a Marito, che Marito...
我带来了衬衫，我想我把它留在了银行。
I brought my shirt, I think I left it in the bank.
Me traje la camiseta, creo que la dejé en el banco.
马里托去看里面，因为那不是。
Marito went to look inside because that was not.
Marito fue a buscar una adentro porque esa no estaba.
我说...
And I said ...
Y yo dije...
混乱。
Chao.
那件衬衫消失了吗？
Did that shirt disappear?
¿Desapareció esa camiseta?
不，我快死了。
No, I'm dying.
No, me muero.
我给了它是因为他们是沟渠，就是这样。
I gave it because they were groap, that's it.
Yo la di porque me la echaron a garear, ya está.
在我看来，这是下一个世界杯之后的下一个电话。
It seems to me that it was the next call, in March, after the World Cup.
Me parece que fue la próxima convocatoria, en marzo, después del Mundial.
我很好地扔了胡安·克鲁兹（Juan Cruz），告诉我，看看我保留了你的东西。
I threw Juan Cruz well and tells me, look at what I kept you.
lo tiré a Juan Cruz bien y me dice, mirá lo que te guardé.
我真的说了... Marito给了我另一个是...
I really say and ... Marito had given me another one that was ...
En serio le digo y... Marito me había dado otra que estaba...
储备，我有两个，但其中之一救了她...
Reserve, I had two, but one of the real had saved her ...
de reserva, yo tenía dos, pero una de la verdadera la había guardado el...
道具，以及我使用过的脚踝靴子，我还保留了它们，所以裂缝。
The props, along with the ankle boots I had used, I had also kept them, so a crack.
El utilero, junto con los botines que había usado, también me los había guardado, así que un crack.
这个孩子是该国最诚实的，因为真相...
This kid is the most honest in the country, because the truth ...
Este pibe es el más honesto del país, porque la verdad...
我可以来那里。
I could have come there.
La podría haber venido ahí.
你卖吗？
Do you sell it?
¿La vendes?
我以为我已经丢了。
I thought I had lost it.
Yo pensé que la había perdido.
那真是太好了！
How nice that!
¡Qué lindo eso!
好吧，你三个更好，我要买你。
Well, you have three better, I'm going to buy you.
Bueno, mejor tenés tres, yo te voy a comprar.
我有30万美元的世界杯T衬衫。
I have $ 300,000 for one of the World Cup t -shirts.
Tengo 300.000 dólares para una de las camisetas del Mundial.
你卖给我吗？
Do you sell it to me?
¿Me la vendes?
不。
No.
$ 300,000。
$ 300,000.
300.000 dólares.
您将乘坐私人飞机去威尼斯。
You are going to Venice by private plane.
Te vas a Venecia en avión privado.
与艾米利亚的下一次旅行乘坐私人飞机，所有付款。
The next trip with Emilia do you by private plane, all payment.
El próximo viaje con Emilia lo haces en avión privado, todo pago.
不，什么都没有发生。
No, nothing happens.
No, no pasa nada.
好吧，500 ...不，600卢卡斯。
Well, 500 ... no, 600 Lucas.
Bueno, 500... No, 600 lucas.
600卢卡斯·格林。
600 Lucas Green.
600 lucas verdes.
$ 600,000。
$ 600,000.
600 000 dólares.
不。
No.
列表。
List.
Listo.
$ 2,600,000。
$ 2,600,000.
2.600.000 dólares.
不，不。
No no.
No, no.
没有机会。
There is no chance.
No hay chance.
七百万美元。
Seven million dollars.
Siete millones de dólares.
不，什么都没有发生。
No, nothing happens.
No, no pasa nada.
不，但是真的，你了解你吗？
No, but really, do you understand you?
No, pero de verdad, te entran, ¿entendés?
但是明天您打开...您有银行的钥匙吗？
But tomorrow you open the ... do you have the bank's key?
Pero mañana abrís el... ¿Vos tenés la clave del banco?
是的。
Yeah.
Sí.
明天你打开钥匙。
Tomorrow you open the key.
Mañana abrís la clave.
他们是四位数。
They are four digits.
Son cuatro dígitos.
我不知道，你打开，你放了，你不知道，你说你有1200。
I don't know, you open, you put and what you had, I don't know, you put that you have 1200.
No sé, abrís, pones y lo que tenías, no sé, pones que tenés 1200.
而且您喜欢这样，他们将7000个，您理解吗？
And you do like this, they put 7000, do you understand?
y haces así, te ponen 7000, ¿entendés?
不，不，不。
No, no, no.
不，我没有那个。
No, I don't have that again.
No, eso no lo vuelvo a tener.
会。
It will.
Se va.
没有理由。
No reason.
Por nada.
然后，我们看看我们是否把这笔钱放在一起。
Then we see if we put that money together.
Después vemos si juntamos esa plata.
那不再恢复了。
That doesn't recover it anymore.
Eso no lo recupera más.
没有机会。
There is no chance.
No hay chance.
所以，拿。
So, take.
Así que, tomá.
运气。
Luck.
Suerte.
多么衬里！
What a lining!
¡Qué forro!
我看到我撞到了那里，……这部分显然不是我的，对吗？
I see that I hit there and ... the part is obvious that it is not mine, right?
Me veo que me pego ahí y... La parte es obvio que no es mío, ¿no?
好吧。
Alright.
Está bien.
太感谢了！
Thank you so much!
¡Muchas gracias!
我麻线！
I take the twine!
¡Me llevo la guita!
对此。
Concorro with this.
Concorro con esto.
切，谢谢，朱利安。
Che, thanks, Julian.
Che, gracias, Julián.
一个荣幸，兄弟。
A pleasure, brother.
Un placer, hermano.
你很好。
That you are very good.
Que estés muy bien.